Guide to the John Paver Papers, 1920-1979 RL.01003
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- National Outdoor Advertising Bureau (NOAB) Files Series
  The National Outdoor Advertising Bureau (NOAB), ca. 1919-1970, the organization with which Paver is most closely associated, was created to help advertisers obtain recognition by billboard owners and to handle arrangements for outdoor advertising. These files date from 1925 through 1968. NOAB was a cooperative organization owned exclusively by the advertising agency members and helped them with all phases of an outdoor campaign. Paver assumed leadership of the agency in 1945, and by 1958 it placed over $70 million in contracts for painted displays, billboards, and other outdoor advertising. He directed the organization for about seventeen years, a time span reflected within the collection, but his time working for the NOAB Field Service Office in the late 1930s is also represented. The papers document his years of leadership through a variety of formats including minutes of NOAB's executive committee from 1950 through the time of his retirement. He represented NOAB through correspondence and multiple speaking engagements, serving often as a cheerleader promoting the industry. The series is arranged alphabetically by subject, revealing information about his travels abroad, contract and policy information, the industry's view of NOAB, Paver's specific duties, poster rates and evaluation, and work for Standard Oil. Particular attention is paid to the Traffic Audit Bureau (TAB) which Paver helped to establish and later defend. TAB became the industry's body to measure circulation of outdoor advertising and is still in existence. Included also are several manuals, some printed materials and other items about or related to NOAB.
  - Accounting Department and Tabulating Department Manual, 1961 (Box 5)
  - Australia Visit, 1953-1960, 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Brennan, John, Correspondence, 1949-1952 (Box 5)
  - Canadian Poster Association Meeting, 1958-1961 (Box 5)
  - Contract Terms, Cancellation Clauses, etc., 1944-1961 and undated (Box 5)
  - Costs, 1962 (Box 5)
  - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes:
    - 1950-1953, 2 folders (Box 5)
    - 1954-1957, 2 folders (Box 6)
    - 1958-1962, 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Field Service Manual, 1938 (Box 6)
  - Field Service Scenario, 1946 (Box 6)
  - International Congress Research and Art Session, 1960 (Box 6)
  - Legislation:
    - 1951 (Box 6)
    - 1957-1968 (Box 6)
  - Media Records, 1954-1956 (Box 6)
  - NOAB, Attitudes Toward and Status, 1960 and undated (Box 6)
  - NOAB Facts, 1949 (Box 6)
  - Operation, Manual of:
    - 1925-1962 (Box 6)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 6)
  - Paver, Services Performed By, 1967, 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Personnel Manual, 1961 (Box 6)
  - Policy Establishment, Report on Hartigan's Proposal, 1961 (Box 6)
  - Poster Billing, 1960-1961[Manual?] (Box 6)
  - Poster Rate Book, 1964, 3 folders (Box 6)
  - Poster Showings Evaluation, 1960-1967 (Box 6)
  - Region One Annual Meeting (Portsmouth, N.H.), 1961 and undated (Box 6)
  - Relationship to Agencies, 1955 (Box 6)
  - Six-sheet and Three-sheet Poster Comments, 1948-1962 (Box 6)
  - Standard Oil File, 1945-1953, 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Statistical Department, Account Supervisor's Manual, 1960-1962 and undated, 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Statistical Market Research, 1947-1962, 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Traffic Audit Bureau (TAB) History:
    - 1931-1963 (Box 7)
    - 1946-1965 (Box 7)
    - 1947-1952 (Box 7)
    - Politz Study, 1954 (Box 7)
  - Traffic Audit Bureau (TAB) Needs and Progress:
    - 1938-1959 (Box 7)
    - 1947-1957, 2 folders (Box 7)
    - 1958-1961 (Box 7)
    - For Chapter on Media:
      - 1948 (Box 7)
      - 1948-1961 (Box 7)
      - 1948-1963 (Box 7)
    - Operating Costs, "Personal," 1948 (Box 7)
  - Traffic Audit Bureau (TAB) Research Institute, Summer Pilot Study, 1936-1965, 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Traffic Counts, Los Angeles, 1962 (Box 7)
  - Workshop, Chicago Outdoor, 1953-1961 (Box 7)
- Subject Files Series
  The Subject Files Series (1920-1972) is arranged alphabetically by topic, proper name, or title, and contains a mix of formats including printed materials, writings, correspondence, and maps. Many folders appear to be collections of research materials for his writing, and all pertain to his professional activities although not always purely outdoor advertising. There are files relating to his window study performed in Allentown, Pa., traffic information for parts of his home state of Texas, auto safety and registration, his writing and publication plans, the "Bull Penn" professional organization, Canadian outdoor advertising, costs, advertising coverage, an international conference, Paver's traffic counting invention (Paver-Sills Traficounter), parking, Paver's work with research associate Leon Quera, awareness of outdoor advertising, regulation of the industry, billboard structure, traffic engineering and safety. Correspondents include the British Poster Advertising Association and other prominent industry figures such as Ben Egan, Karl Eller (Eller Media), and T. Walter Tyrrell.
  - Advertising Research Foundation, 1957 and undated (Box 7)
  - Allentown, Pa. (See also Data):
    - Maps and Data, 1936 and undated (Box 7)
    - Statistical Tables, undated (Box 7)
    - Window Study, 1936 (Box 7)
  - American Marketing Association, 1962-1966 (Box 7)
  - American Security Council, 1970 (Box 7)
  - A.N.A. [Association of National Advertisers?] Members and Non-members, undated (Box 7)
  - Audit Procedures, 1933-1934 (Box 7)
  - Austin Transportation Study, 1962 (Box 7)
  - Australia and Japan Correspondence, 1958-1961 (Box 7)
  - Auto Registration Growth, 1963 and undated (Box 7)
  - Auto Safety Foundation, 1969 (Box 7)
  - Book Correspondence:
    - 1954-1964 (Box 7)
    - 1964 (Box 7)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 7)
  - Bowack, Charles, 1958 (Box 7)
  - British Poster Advertising Association, 1962-1972 (Box 7)
  - Bull Penn:
    - 1939-1949, 2 folders (Box 7)
    - 1939-1949, 2 folders (Box 8)
    - 1945-1959 (Box 8)
    - Personnel, 1949-1960 (Box 8)
  - C-V Rating, 1930 (Box 8)
  - Canadian Methods, 1971 (Box 8)
  - Cost of Outdoor Advertising, 1933-1934 (Box 8)
  - Cost of Outdoor vs. Newspaper, [ca. 1962] (Box 8)
  - Coverage and Capacity, 1953 (Box 8)
  - Coverage, 1960 and undated (Box 8)
    (See also Los Angeles, San Francisco, and Seattle)
  - Data, [Allentown, Pa.?] undated (Box 8)
  - Driver Training Information, 1968-1970 (Box 8)
  - Egan, Ben - Correspondence, 1963-1965 (Box 8)
  - Eller, Karl:
    - Correspondence, 1971 (Box 8)
    - Correspondence and TAB Reorganization, 1971 and undated (Box 8)
  - Engineer Registration, 1969-1970 (Box 8)
  - Foreign Correspondence, 1960 (Box 8)
  - Foreign Market Advertising:
    - 1963-1964 (Box 8)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 8)
  - Fresno Growth Appraisal and Department of Commerce Correspondence, 1932-1936 (Box 8)
  - Gasoline Business Survey, [1946?] (Box 8)
  - Hendon, Don - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 8)
  - Hodges, J. (M. Gen.), 1962-1971 (Box 8)
  - Insurance Institute for Traffic Safety:
    - 1967-1970, 2 folders (Box 8)
    - 1970-1972, 2 folders (Box 8)
  - International Advertising, 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - International Conference-- Toronto-- Correspondence, 1958-1960 (Box 8)
  - International Congress, 1960 (Box 8)
  - International Congress--Publicity, 1960 (Box 8)
  - International Congress--Slide Correspondence, 1960 (Box 8)
  - International Executive Service Corp., 1969 and undated (Box 8)
  - International Poster Statistics, 1961 (Box 8)
  - London--Canada Study and Window Display Research, 1935 (Box 8)
  - Los Angeles Coverage:
    - 1960 (Box 8)
    - [1961?] (Box 9)
  - McGraw-Hill Agreements, 1967-1968 (Box 9)
  - Media and Advertising Costs, 1964 and undated (Box 9)
  - Media Costs, 1965 (Box 9)
  - Merchandising, 1958-1964 (Box 9)
  - Mills and Rockley's Ltd., 1963-1966 (Box 9)
  - New Jersey State Survey, 1934-1952 (Box 9)
  - Newspaper vs. Outdoor, undated (Box 9)
  - Outdoor Advertising Association of America, 1960-1964 (Box 9)
  - Paint Pricing History, 1934 and undated (Box 9)
  - Parking Terminals and Facilities Committee, 1938-1940, 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Paver--Sills Traficounter:
    (See also small round box within box 19)
    - 1938-1941 (Box 9)
    - [1939?] (Box 9)
    - 1940 and undated (Box 9)
    - 1940-1941 and undated, 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Permissions, 1964-1969 (Box 9)
  - Post Cereals, [1961?] (Box 9)
  - P.P.S. [Portable Parking Structures] Inc., 1969 (Box 9)
  - Promotion Correspondence, 1945-1946 (Box 9)
  - Publisher Correspondence, 1967-1969, 3 folders (Box 9)
  - Quera, Leon, 1967-1970 (Box 9)
  - Quera, Leon - "The Quera Mess:"
    - 1966-1969 (Box 9)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 9)
    - 1968 (Box 9)
    - 1968 (Box 9)
  - Recognition / Awareness of Outdoor Advertising, 1962 (Box 9)
  - Regulation of Industry:
    - 1961-1970 (Box 9)
    - 1964-1968 (Box 9)
    - 1970 (Box 9)
  - Regulation of Industry and OAAA, 1965-1968 (Box 9)
  - Remembrance and Forgetting, [1960s?] (Box 9)
  - Research Processes, 1948-1963 (Box 9)
  - Retail Store Locations, [1936?] (Box 9)
  - Sales, Local, 1959-1965 and undated (Box 9)
  - San Francisco Coverage - Oakland, 1961 (Box 10)
  - Seattle Poster Coverage, 1962-1965 (Box 10)
  - Sills Correspondence, 1958-1961 (Box 10)
  - Small Business Administration, 1968 (Box 10)
  - Standridge, R.H., Correspondence, 1972 (Box 10)
  - Structural and Posting Illustrations, 1936-1970 (Box 10)
  - Texas:
    - Research League, 1967 (Box 10)
    - State Government, 1971 (Box 10)
    - Tourist Development Agency, 1963-1971 (Box 10)
  - Traffic and Parking Problem, 1939-1967 and undated (Box 10)
  - Traffic and Trade (Atwater correspondence), 1936-1959 (Box 10)
  - Traffic Data, Los Angeles, 1920-1936 (Box 10)
  - Traffic Deaths, 1967 (Box 10)
  - Traffic Engineering and Methods, 1936 (Data and Field Records, Allentown, Pa.) (Box 10)
  - Traffic Formula--DEC vs. Reach, 1968 (Box 10)
  - Traffic - Gulf Study, 1936-1939 and undated (Box 10)
  - Traffic Miscellaneous, 1940 and undated (Box 10)
  - Traffic Safety:
    - 1966-1968 (Box 10)
    - 1966-1971 (Box 10)
    - 1966-1970 (Box 10)
  - Traffic Safety, Austin and Texas:
    - 1971, 3 folders (Box 10)
    - 1969-1971 (Box 10)
  - Traffic Study, 1940-1961 (Box 10)
  - Traffic Summaries, Oklahoma, 1960 (Box 10)
  - Tyrrell, T. Walter, Correspondence:
    - 1968-1970 (Box 10)
    - 1970-1972 (Box 10)
  - Urban Development, 1937-1964 (Box 10)
  - Valuation, undated (Box 10)
  - Values of Outdoor Advertising, 1965 and undated (Box 10)
  - Window Display Research, 1936 (Box 10)
    (See also Allentown, Pa., and London-Canada)
  - Wray, James R., Correspondence, 1971 (Box 10)
  - Yale University, Bureau of Highway Traffic, 1945-1961 (Box 10)
- Personal Files Series
  The Personal Files Series (1943-1979) reveals a wide breadth of activity beyond Paver's professional duties. Materials document relationships with family members as well as connections to such organizations as the Freemasons, Paver's church, and the Chicago Athletic Association. Most prominent is documentation of his time spent raising orchids, including newsletters, photographs, and correspondence with the American Orchid Society.
  - Chicago Athletic Association, 1947 (Box 10)
  - Church, 1965-1967 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence:
    - 1943-1968, 2 folders (Box 10)
    - 1958-1967 (Box 11)
  - Davis, Guy W., 1963-1966 (Box 11)
  - Freemasons, 1964-1968 (Box 11)
  - Hawaii, 1962-1963 (Box 11)
  - Kauai, 1963 (Box 11)
  - Kauai Development, 1963-1964 (Box 11)
  - Kauai Real Estate, 1962-1963 (Box 11)
  - Mine, 1962-1967 (Box 11)
  - Orchids:
    - American Orchid Society, 1972 (Box 11)
    - Correspondence and Lists, 1971 (Box 11)
    - Correspondence with Lager and Horrell, 1956-1972 (Box 11)
    - Cymbidiums, 1969 (Box 11)
    - Garden Clubs, 1967-1979 (Box 11)
    - ...of Hawaii, 1971 (Box 11)
    - Hawaii Island Chamber of Commerce, 1971 (Box 11)
    - Import Procedures, 1968 and undated (Box 11)
    - [Koalin?]--Prices, undated (Box 11)
    - McBeans, 1969-1970 (Box 11)
    - Periodicals, 1967-1972 (Box 11)
    - Periodicals, 1970-1972 (Box 11)
    - Periodicals, 1970 (Box 11)
    - Soil and Plant, 1971 (Box 11)
  - Red Bud Trail Repair, 1971-1972 (Box 11)
  - Rotary Club, 1970 (Box 11)
  - Rotary International, 1968-1970 (Box 11)
  - Solar Power, 1966-1969 (Box 11)
  - Solar Power, 1966 (Box 11)
  - West Lake Hills, 1966 (Box 11)
- Miscellaneous Files Series
  The Miscellaneous Files Series contains additional materials for all of the previous series including speeches, professional correspondence, personal wartime correspondence, writings, printed materials, and clippings. These originally loose items were placed in unsorted folders for protection, but at the time of processing, resources were unavailable for item-level identification and sorting. Topics include outdoor advertising in the U.S. and abroad; traffic safety, circulation, and engineering; biographical materials; TAB, OAAA, and NOAB; military orders and service during WWII; outdoor advertising construction, product name recall, reach and frequency; costs; the "Bull Penn;" and orchids.
  - Miscellaneous (unsorted) Files, 11 folders (Box 11)
  - Miscellaneous (unsorted) Files, 21 folders (Box 12)
  - Miscellaneous (unsorted) Files, 25 folders (Box 13)
  - Miscellaneous (unsorted) Files, 19 folders (Box 14)
  - Miscellaneous (unsorted) Files, 39 folders (Box 15)
  - Miscellaneous (unsorted) Files, 11 folders (Box 16)
- Photographs, Negatives, and Slides Series
  The Photographs, Negatives, and Slides Series (ca. 1920s-1970) contains over 300 items, pulled together from all other parts of the collection. A few photographs are from the 1920s, but the majority appear to have been taken in the 1950s and 1960s.They document a great deal of outdoor advertising mounted in that era, and also provide evidence of other areas of Paver's life such as his garden work. Most are undated (color or black and white) photographs of outdoor advertising, especially billboards, but there are also a large number of portraits of Paver from the 1940s and 1950s. Some photographs show advertising artwork and artists at work on large painted displays, and some seem to form part of an office presentation. Other photograph subjects include office workers demonstrating particular activities; business gatherings of various sorts; advertising in Paris and an Asian city (perhaps in Japan), and a wedding gathering. Around 40 photographs show Paver's pool area, where he worked with and displayed his collection of orchids.
  More detailed information about all photographs, slides, and negatives were entered into the Resource for Outdoor Advertising Descriptions (ROAD) database which will be available in early 2003. The database has the following information fields: image number, dates, image type, product category, company, product/brand, headline, advertisement type, posting company, image color, rural or city scene, ethnicity of some individuals, presence of women/children, famous persons, city, state, non-advertisement type, and additional notes.
  - Photographs and Slides, 117 pages of sleeves (Box 17)
    [ ROAD Database Numbers: PAV0001-PAV0202]
  - Photographs, and Negatives, 55 pages of sleeves (Box 18)
    [ ROAD Database Numbers: PAV0203-PAV0326]
- Legal Size Materials
  The Legal Size Materials include items from all of the other series, except Photographs, Negatives, and Slides.
  - Biographical Information (see also series: Biographical Files): (Box 19)
    - Miscellaneous Biographical Information, 1962 and undated (Box 19)
  - Writings and Speeches by Paver (see also series: Writings and Speeches by Paver):
    - Textbook Files:
      (alphabetical by subject, and then by book segment)
      - Customized Buying, Fragments (miscellaneous), 1969 (Box 19)
      - Painted Displays, Typescripts with Some Holograph Edits, undated (Box 19)
      - Public Relations/Criticism, Typescript with Holograph Edits, undated (Box 19)
      - TAB Program, 1964-1971 (Box 19)
      - Variation of Values-- Holograph and Typescript Fragments with Holograph Edits, 2 folders (Box 19)
      - Appendix, undated (Box 19)
      - Illustrations, Chapter I, 1965-1968 (Box 19)
      - Outline of Advertising Techniques, undated (Box 19)
      - Outlines for Textbook, undated (Box 19)
      - Questionnaire Results, "The Medium," 1968 (Box 19)
      - Questionnaire Results, 1968 (Box 19)
      - Fragments (Miscellaneous):
        - 1957 and undated (Box 19)
        - 1960-1969 (Box 19)
        - 1962, 1965 and undated (Box 19)
        - undated, 2 folders (Box 19)
      - Typescript Fragments (Miscellaneous):
        - 1933-1962 and undated (Box 19)
        - undated (Box 19)
      - Volume II: Research Typescripts and Poster Site Surveys, 1966 and undated (Box 19)
    - Speech Files:
      - Speeches, Miscellaneous:
        - 1960-1961 (Box 19)
        - 1962 and undated (Box 19)
    - Miscellaneous Files:
      - Economical Coverage Manuscripts, 1935, 3 folders (Box 19)
  - Writings and Speeches by Others (see also series: Writings and Speeches by Others):
    - Dawson, Joe M., Speeches Miscellaneous, 1947 (Box 19)
    - Hopkins, Frank T., Speeches, 1936-1940 (Box 19)
    - Fragments, Miscellaneous, 1963-1967 (Box 19)
  - National Outdoor Advertising Bureau Files (see also series: National Outdoor Advertising Bureau Files):
    - Agency Study, undated (Box 19)
    - Market Research, Statistical, 1945-1957 (Box 19)
    - Newsletters, 1946-1947 and undated (Box 19)
    - TAB History, 1963 (Box 19)
    - TAB Research Institute, Summer Pilot Study, 1971 and undated (Box 19)
  - Subject Files (see also series: Subject Files):
    - Book Correspondence, undated (Box 19)
    - British Poster Advertising Association, undated (Box 19)
    - Canadian Methods, 1971 (Box 19)
    - Chicago Subway College Thesis, 1923 and undated (Box 19)
    - Cost of Outdoor Advertising, [1960s] (Box 19)
    - Engineering Applications, [1966?] (Box 19)
    - Foreign Market Advertising, 1963-1966, 2 folders (Box 19)
    - International Executive Service Office Corp., undated (Box 19)
    - McGraw-Hill Agreements, 1967-1968 (Box 19)
    - Media and Advertising Facts, 1961 (Box 19)
    - Nokes, Thomas, undated (Box 19)
    - Outdoor Advertising Association of America - Outdoor Advertising Regulations, 1961-1970 (Box 19)
    - P.P.S. [Portable Parking Structures] Inc., 1969 (Box 19)
    - Phillips Foundation, Correspondence Drafts, undated (Box 19)
    - Quera, Leon, 1967 (Box 19)
    - Quera, Leon, "The Quera Mess," 1967-1968 (Box 19)
    - Small Business Administration, undated (Box 19)
    - Standridge, R.H., Correspondence, undated (Box 19)
    - State-City Traffic Safety:
      - [1951-1966 or later] (Box 19)
      - 1971 (Box 19)
    - Texas Tourist Development Agency, 1963-1971 (Box 19)
    - Traffic Information, undated (Box 19)
  - Personal Files (see also series: Personal Files):
    - Church, 1965-1967 (Box 19)
    - Hawaii, 1962-1963 (Box 19)
    - Hodges, J. (M.Gen.), 1962-1971 (Box 19)
    - Kauai Development, 1963 (Box 19)
    - Kauai Real Estate, 1962-1963 (Box 19)
    - Orchids - Correspondence with Lager and Horrell, 1956-1972 (Box 19)
    - Orchids--Garden Clubs, 1967 (Box 19)
    - Red Bud Trail Repair, 1971-1972 (Box 19)
    - West Lake Hills, 1966 (Box 19)
  - Miscellaneous Files (see also series: Miscellaneous Files):
    - Miscellaneous, 6 folders (Box 19)
    - Miscellaneous, 12 folders (Box 20)
    - Traficounter tape (Box 20)
- Oversize Materials
  The Oversize Materials include items from all of the other series, except the Biographical Files Series, and the Photographs, Negatives, and Slides Series.
  - Writings and Speeches by Paver (see also series: Writings and Speeches by Paver): (Box 21)
    - Determination of Allotments, Typescript and Fragments, 1968 (Box 21)
    - Media Selection, Typescript with Holograph Edits, undated (Box 21)
    - MONI [Metropolitan Outdoor Network, Inc.] and National Sales, Typescripts, undated (Box 21)
    - Public Relations, Typescript with Holograph Edits, 1963-1972 (Box 21)
    - Appendix, 1936 (Box 21)
    - Forms, 1938-1968 (Box 21)
    - Typescript Fragments (Misc.):
      - 1933-1962, 2 folders (Box 21)
      - 1960-1969 (Box 21)
      - 1963-1967 (Box 21)
      - undated, 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Volume II: Table of Contents, Typescript and Additional Fragments, undated (Box 21)
  - National Outdoor Advertising Bureau Files (see also series: National Outdoor Advertising Bureau Files):
    - Poster Showings, Evaluation, undated (Box 21)
    - TAB (Traffic Audit Bureau) History, 1929 and undated, 2 folders (Box 21)
    - TAB (Traffic Audit Bureau) Needs and Progress, 1938 (Box 21)
  - Subject Files (see also series: Subject Files):
    - C-V Rating, undated (Box 21)
    - Chicago Subway College Thesis, [1924?],and State-City Traffic Safety, 1971 (Box 21)
    - Clippings, 1938-1969 (Box 21)
    - Foreign Market Advertising, 1962 (Box 21)
    - London-Canada Study, 1935 and undated (Box 21)
    - Outdoor Advertising Values, 1964,and Traffic, Gulf Study, undated (Box 21)
    - Traffic Formula-DEC [Daily Effective Circulation] vs. Research, 1968 and undated,and Sales, Local, undated (Box 21)
    - Transportation Information, 1939 and undated (Box 21)
    - Valuation, undated (Box 21)
  - Personal Files (see also series: Personal Files): (Box 22)
    - Northwestern Transcript, 1920-1925and Publicity, 1927-1965 (Box 22)
    - Kauai, 1963and Hawaii, 1962-1963 (Box 22)
  - Miscellaneous Files (see also series: Miscellaneous Files):
    - Miscellaneous, 7 folders (Box 22)
  - Writings and Speeches (see also series: Writings and Speeches by Paver and Others): (Oversize-folder 1)
    - Chart, undated (Box 23)
    - Variation of Values, undated (Box 23)
  - Subject Files (see also series: Subject Files): (Box 23)
    - Allentown, Pa. - Median Values of Homes; Purchasing Power; Family Card, 1930 and undated (Box 23)
    - Audit Procedures, undated (Box 23)
    - Detroit Market, 1945 and undated (Box 23)
    - Maps: Allentown, Pa., undated (Box 23)
    - N.J. State Survey, undated (Box 23)
    - Traffic Summaries--Okla., 1957 (Box 23)
    - Window Study-- Allentown, Pa., 1938 and undated (Box 23)
  - Miscellaneous Files (see also series: Miscellaneous Files) (Box 23)